# **Monica Worek**

## Staff Pharmacist - Albert Einstein Medical Center

West Deptford, NJ - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Monica-Worek/82d4469a9df08cc2

Received Doctor of Pharmacy Degree December 2009. Strong background in drug utilization review, intravenous therapy and compounding. My experience includes but is not limited to: Hospital pharmacy practice, customer service, managed care, mail service, home infusion pharmacy practice and hospice pharmacy. I possess excellent written and verbal communication skills.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

#### **Staff Pharmacist**

Albert Einstein Medical Center - Philadelphia, PA - 2010 to Present

3rd Shift

Medication order review, interventions and dispensing, parenteral compounding, controlled substance dispensing and inventory, unit dose preparation, drug information functions, supervision of technical staff.

#### **Staff Pharmacist**

Underwood Memorial Hospital - Woodbury, NJ - 2004 to Present

Physician order review and entry; prescription dispensing; outpatient prescription dispensing; intravenous admixtures and hyperalimentation compounding; order review; drug utilization review and intervention; pharmacokinetic monitoring; controlled substance inventory and dispensing; unit dose preparation; Pyxis functions; staff education; supervision of technical staff; patient counseling

- Member of a lean six sigma team for respiratory therapy process improvement. The team was able to redesign the workflow for the respiratory therapists to provide better, more timely and more effective patient care.
- Third shift supervisor for the majority of my employment at Underwood Memorial Hospital.

## **Clinical Pharmacist**

Enclara Health - West Deptford, NJ - 2009 to 2010

Medication order receipt and review, pain and symptom consultation, medication verification and dispensing, extemporaneous compounding, phone consults with physicians and nursing staff regarding patient care, patient counseling, staff education.

# Staff Pharmacist

Memorial Hospital of Salem County - Salem, NJ - 2003 to 2005

Clinical functions and intervention; physician order review and entry; nursing unit inspections; controlled substance inventory and dispensing; prescription dispensing; unit dose preparation; intravenous admixture and hyperalimentation compounding; drug utilization review; medication cassette verification; Pyxis functions; technical staff supervision; patient counseling

• Adjunct member of the Pharmacotherapeutics committee.

## **Staff Pharmacist**

Medco Health Solutions - Willingboro, NJ - 2002 to 2003

Prescription dispensing; drug product verification; drug information; customer service functions; quality assurance; drug utilization review and intervention; technical staff supervision; patient counseling

## Staff Pharmacist- night shift

Virtua Health System - Marlton, NJ - 2000 to 2002

Intravenous admixtures and hyperalimentation compounding; medication order review and entry; prescription dispensing; clinical functions; drug use evaluation and intervention; controlled substance inventory and dispensing; unit dose preparation; medication cassette verification, technical staff supervision.

### Staff IV Admixture Pharmacist

Medilink Homecare - Hammonton, NJ - 1999 to 2000

Intravenous medication and hyperalimentation compounding and preparation; physician liaison; patient counseling; customer service; prescription dispensing; medication procurement; utilization review and intervention; supervision of technical staff; coordination of daily and weekly deliveries to patient homes and physician offices.

#### Staff Pharmacist

NeighborCare - King of Prussia, PA - 1997 to 1999

Physician order review and entry; clinical review of physician orders; prescription dispensing; controlled substance inventory, procurement and dispensing; extemporaneous compounding; unit dose packaging; supervision of technical staff; customer service; patient counseling; coordination of deliveries to nursing homes during the overnight hours; intravenous medication preparation and dispensing.

• Night shift supervisor

# **Staff Pharmacist**

Diversified Prescription Delivery - Horsham, PA - 1995 to 1997

Prescription review and dispensing; drug utilization review and intervention; customer service, patient counseling; dispensing, procurement and inventory management of Class II controlled substances; extemporaneous compounding; quality assurance.

# Staff Pharmacist

National Rx Services - Mechanicsburg, PA - 1992 to 1995

Prescription review and medication dispensing, drug utilization review and intervention, customer service, patient counseling, managed care functions; high cost injectable medication procurement and dispensing.

#### **Staff Pharmacist**

Milton S. Hershey Medical Center - Hershey, PA - 1991 to 1992

Intravenous admixtures; hyperalimentation preparation and compounding; patient consultations and counseling; decentralized pharmacy operations; medication dispensing; extemporaneous compounding of medications; chemotherapy preparation and compounding; outpatient prescription dispensing; technical staff supervision.

## **EDUCATION**

# **Doctor of Pharmacy**

University of Florida - Gainesville, FL 2009

#### **Bachelor of Science**

Philadelphia College of Pharmacy and Science - Philadelphia, PA 1991

## Diploma in Academic

Bishop Conwell High School - Levittown, PA 1986